Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Audio recordings
  - Subseries A: Audio elements
    - Title: Water, [1974]; cuid23034 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0105)
      Annotations: (on container:) Water / GB-Duka-AC 74 // (on cassette:) A: Early water / B: Water GB/AC/DUKA
    - Title: AC Teaching Watercolor, Unkown; cuid23035 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0106)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) AC Teaching watercolor
    - Title: [1]-- Rapallo [2]-- Florence, Unknown; cuid23036 (Box 23, Folder ID: 156.0107)
      Annotations: (On cassette:) A: Plat(?) Rapallo / B: Florence
- Series XI: Film
  Film materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    - Flourescent/ Azalea, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1976; ID: 156.0153 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0153)
      Gauge: 16mm, color, sound
      Duration: 00:04:00
    - Fluorescent/ Azalea - Answer Print, ID: 156.0162 (Reel 156.0162)
      Gauge: 16mm
    - Fluorescent/Azalea - Release Print, ID: 156.0163 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 156.0163)
    - 11 thru 12, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1977; ID: 156.0152 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0152)
    - 11 thru 12 - Color Answer Print, ID: 156.0154 (Reel 156.0154)
      Gauge: 16mm, color
    - 11 thru 12 - Release Print, ID: 156.0155 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 156.0155)
    - Flora Funera - Answer Print (2011 Restoration), ID: 156.0172 (Reel 156.0172)
    - Lost Shoe Blues - Answer Print (2011 Restoration), ID: 156.0167 (Reel 156.0167)
    - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert (2015 Restoration), circa 1976; cuid23214 (Shelf Media)
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert, circa 1976; cuid23043 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0114, Media 156.0114)
      Alternate title: [Some Food May Be Found in the Desert]
      Gauge: Super8mm
      Footage count: [200 ft.]
      Extent: 1/1
      Annotations: Reshoot Trash sequence w Kodachrome - get scratched feet repaired - add words to sound: Fake Beach; East River Dump; Dead Fish; Broken Glass + Ice; Bells; Firecrackers (Some Food May Be Found In The Desert)
      Access DVDs (2 copies) available.
      Content Notes
      [1]-- Fake Beach [2]-- East River Dump [3]-- Dead Fish [4]-- Broken Glass + Ice [5]-- Bells [6]-- Firecrackers
    - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert [Preservation], 2015; 1976; 5 film reels Four 16mm preservation film elements
      - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert [Release Print], cuid23211 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 156.0174)
      - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert [Color Internegative], cuid23209 (Reel 156.0176)
      - Some Food May Be Found in the Desert [Optical Track], cuid23210 (Reel 156.0177)
    - Outside Noticing, Jan. 1976, (date of film); cuid23037 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0108)
      Alternate title: [children with microphone]
      Annotations: "Outside Noticing" Jan '76
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23038 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0109)
      Footage count: [400 ft.]
    - [1]-- Lost Shoe Blues [2]-- Flora Funera (For Battery Park City, (date of film); cuid23039 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0110)
      18 fps
      Annotations: Unknown
      Alternate Title: [Untitled - Landscape with Different Plants]
    - New Jersey Night Fish; [1]--A Jumpery [2]--Rubber Glove Plays Ruler Piano For Measuring Mind [2a]--Flower/Azalea + By Stratch [3]--A Jimps In Cadeana, (date of film); cuid23040 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0111)
      Alternate title: [New Jersey Night Fish]
    - [1]-- A asks if she can get 2 something to drink [ 2]-- Race cars [3]--. Sunglasses [4]-- Truck + pool in Muncie, (date of film); cuid23041 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0112)
      Alternate title: Bathtub Movie
      Annotations: 1. A asks if she can get 2 something to drink - Brick + STEAM / 2. Race cars/ 3. Sunglasses/ 4. Truck + pool in Muncie // Bath tub movie / dog in truck/ Fred's sound recording experiments
    - Silent Selections, (date of film); cuid23042 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0113)
      Footage count: [100 ft.]
      Annotations: Silent Selections
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23044 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0115)
      Alternate Title: [Air Travel; Nicaragua and/or USSR]
    - #3, (date of film); cuid23045 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0116)
      Annotations: Date: #3
    - Utah MRM, (date of film); cuid23046 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0117)
      Annotations: Utah MRM
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23047 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0118)
      Alternate title: [Untitled - Flowers on Trees]
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23048 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0119)
      Annotations: (on reel:) Reel 2
      Alternate title: [Untitled - Painting and Firedrill]
    - Ailanthus Film Samples, (date of film); cuid23049 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0120)
      Annotations: 5645 // A. Callard Ailanthus Film Samples (print) Box 37 NYC 10013 212 925-8974
    - Florida, (date of film); cuid23050 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0121)
      Annotations: Florida - Orig
    - 11 thru 12, (date of film); cuid23051 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0122)
      Footage count: [200 ft]
      Annotations: 11 - 12 Super 8mm ^ 160 feet. Orig. // feature // 4257
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23052 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0123)
      Annotations: same as 156.0122
      Alternate title: "Andrea Callard Notes on Ailanthus 10 Min. 18 Frames No Sound"
    - Untitled, (date of film); cuid23053 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0124)
    - Red Film, (date of film); cuid23054 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0125)
      Footage count: [150 ft.]
      Annotations: Red Film
    - Standard Adult Wheelchar; Temporary Participation For An Analogous Situation, (date of film); cuid23055 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0126)
      Annotations: Standard Adult Wheelchar; Temporary Participation For An Analogous Situation; Super 8, sound, color, 18 FPS ^6 minutes running time
    - Alfred Hitchcock's Psycho, (date of film); cuid23056 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0127)
      Annotations: Alfred Hitchcock's Psycho / Castle Films
    - Ekta Underwater, (date of film); cuid23057 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0128)
      Footage count: [50 ft.]
      Annotations: Ekta Underwater
    - Hostage Parade - Street thru Roof, (date of film); cuid23058 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0129)
      Annotations: [Geller] Hostage Parade - street thru roof
    - Silent Hostage Trash Ends, (date of film); cuid23059 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0130)
      Annotations: Callard Silent Hostage Trash Ends
    - 360, (date of film); cuid23060 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0131)
      Annotations: 360
    - [1]--Bay Bridge [2]-- Crossing Water [3]-- Eucalyptus [4]-- Lamp Reflect [5]-- Fog, (date of film); cuid23061 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0132)
      Annotations: Bay Bridge; Crossing Water; Eucalyptus; Lamp Reflect; Fog
    - Beach Birds 76/77, (date of film); cuid23062 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0133)
      Alternate title: [11 thru 12 outtakes]
      Annotations: Beach Birds 76 77
    - Wires: Linera Division of Landscape, (date of film); cuid23063 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0134)
      Annotations: Wires: Linera Division of Landscape
    - Gull Takes Off, (date of film); cuid23064 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0135)
      Annotations: Gull Takes Off
    - Water Tower Workers, (date of film); cuid23065 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0136)
      Annotations: Water Tower Workers
    - Dog Play, (date of film); cuid23066 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0137)
      Footage count: [25 ft.]
      Annotations: Dog Play
    - 1 Water Tower, (date of film); cuid23067 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0138)
      Annotations: 1 Water Tower
    - [1]-- Portotino [2]-- Water [3]-- Lion [4]-- Commie [5]-- Clouds, (date of film); cuid23068 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0139)
      Annotations: 4 Portotino; Water; Lion; Commie; Clouds
    - Bodies at Leisure, Ch. Beach '79, (date of film); cuid23069 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0140)
      Annotations: Bodies at Leisure, Ch. Beach 79
    - Hostage Parade, (date of film); cuid23070 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0141)
      Annotations: Hostage Parade
    - Water Exp., (date of film); cuid23071 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0142)
      Annotations: Water exp
    - F/A, (date of film); cuid23072 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0143)
      Annotations: F/A
    - Delaware Stone Throw; July 4, 1975, (date of film); cuid23073 (Box 24, Folder ID: 156.0144)
      Annotations: Delaware Stone Throw 4 July '75
    - [1]-- City Scenes, Rooftops, Foliage, cuid23215; 4 film reels Super 8mm (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - [2]-- Outside Lincoln Tunnel, Fall, Red, cuid23216 (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - [3]-- Rooftops, cuid23217 (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - [4]-- Flowers, Mish-mash, Fossil Seed Debris, cuid23218 (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - [5]-- Rhododendrons, Azaleas, cuid23219 (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - [6]-- Windows, F/A outtakes, cuid23220 (Box Shared Fales 090)
    - Fluorescent/Azalea Magnetic Soundtrack, cuid23221 (Box Shared Fales 090)
- Oversize
  Oversize material is arranged by series. The folder number relates the folder to the material's location in the larger collection sequence.
  - Series I Subseries A: Colab Administrative materials
    - Andrea Callard's secretarial notebook; miscellaneous fragments, loose., undated; cuid23074 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Money disbursement and budget, 1977-1980; cuid23075 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Series I Subseries B: Colab Shows and Events
    - Animals Living in Cities at Fashion Moda. poster, 1979; cuid23076 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Times Square Show advertisements. June 1980 at 7th Avenue and 41st St., cuid23077 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Three Times Square Show posters by Reese Williams., 1980; cuid23078 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Times Square Show Poster by Jane Dickson and Charlie Ahearn, 1980; cuid23079 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Times Square Show press, 1980; cuid23080 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Animals Living in Cities at ABC NO RIO. newsprint announcement. Includes AC drawing from Ailanthus project., 1980; cuid23081 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Teu-Gum Show Poster. Geneva Switzerland., 1981; cuid23082 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - "Colab Hits the Ritz" poster. Colaboration between Colab and the Washington Project for the Arts. Washington DC., 1983; cuid23083 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Metropolis M german language periodical, no 4 November 1983. "Colab Kunst en de Lower East Side", cuid23084 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - A. More Store advertisement in Artforum, 1984; cuid23085 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Up with People: An exhibition of graphics. 8 December-7 January at Concord Gallery NYC., 1984; cuid23086 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Poster: White Columns Interactive Video Screening Party. Includes Potato Wolf., undated; cuid23087 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Series II Subseries B: Andrea Callard Artist Files 1973-1976, 150 Chambers St.
    - Experiences Vacuume. Black and white photographs., cuid23088 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Charting the Siberian Mountains., 1975; cuid23089 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - AC in costume. Black and white photographs., 1973-1976; cuid23090 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - notes for "A Dressing Wall" work., 1973-1976; cuid23091 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Red Anger Association. Polaroid photographs in cardboard frame., 1973-1976; cuid23092 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Miscellaneous pencil drawings. no specific dates. located temorally through photographs as ca. 1973-1976., cuid23093 (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - background drawing, white paper and black ink., 1973-1976; cuid23094 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Page of art notebook, coffee and pencil. "a relaxed hand would not make such marks...", 1973-1976; cuid23095 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Series II Subseries C: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1976-1978 40 Lispenard St.
    - City canoe black and white photos with captions., 1977; cuid23096 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Ciy Canoe black and white photographs, rejects and printing information., 1977; cuid23097 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Bat pamphlet original. AC's contribution to Colab's batman show in Robin Winters loft 591 Broadway., 1977; cuid23098 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Black and White still from "Standard Adult Wheelchair: Temporary participation for an analogous situation", 1977; cuid23099 (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Cummington, MA: exposed pipe, building interior., 1978; cuid23100 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Andrea Callard and Fred Krughoof mind/heart photo collages., 1978; cuid23101 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Ailanthus Questionnaires, blank., 1978; cuid23102 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Completed Ailanthus Questionnaires., 1978; cuid23103 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Ailanthus Grove main plan. Black and white photos with hand coloring in large display book. Loose images and envelope of captions. Copyright September 1978., cuid23104 (Box 14, Folder 187)
      Metal, photographs sleeved in brittle plastic.
    - Ailanthus Grove main plan. Black and white photos with hand coloring. Loose images only. Copyright September 1978., cuid23105 (Box 13, Folder 187B)
    - Ailanthus, spraypaint and stencil with caption "Concentrate on Joy/ Nature is the boss/ Let's cross-polinate", 1977-1984; cuid23106 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Ailanthus and trashbags, watercolor, 1977-1984; cuid23107 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Color photographs of Ailanthus and cynthia moths with text on clear plastic overlay, 1977-1984; cuid23108 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Gridded paper with captions, glue marks and pencil. Used for Ailanthus projects., 1977-1984; cuid23109 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - Ailanthus black and white contact sheets., 1977-1984; cuid23110 (Box 13, Folder 197)
    - The Ailanthus family spread, Black and white hand tinted photographs with elictrical tape., 1977-1984; cuid23111 (Box 13, Folder 198)
    - Ailanthus drawings, 1977-1984; cuid23112 (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - Series II Subseries D: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1979-1981 40 Lispenard St.
    - "All Animals Need Water to Survive" Andrea Callard's contribution to Colab's "Animals Living in the City" show.Color photographs on paper with text. Original, 1979; cuid23113 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Ailanthus project, Seed machine photograph., 1979; cuid23114 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Andrea Callard's proposal photo collages for the Custom and Culture II show, organized by Creative Time, 1979; cuid23115 (Box 15, Folder 211)
    - Original collage black and white photographs with hand tinting from AC's Custom and Culture II piece., 1979; cuid23116 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white contact sheet. Images of stairs, windows, lighting, ornaments. See folder 218 for smaller contact sheet and negatives of the same images., 1979; cuid23117 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white contact sheets. Images of building exteriors. see folder 229 for corresponding negatives., 1979; cuid23118 (Box 15, Folder 228)
    - "Commuting from Point to Point" color photograph., 1980; cuid23119 (Box 15, Folder 242)
    - Andrea Callard's contribution to the Brooke Alexander Colab Benefit. Cold foil and paint, 1980; cuid23120 (Box 15, Folder 250)
    - News and Nutrition work. Andrea Callard's contribution the Colab's Times Square Show., 1980; cuid23121 (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - Planning notes for News and Nutrition work., 1980; cuid23122 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Photo background used for News and Nutrition work., 1980; cuid23123 (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - Newspaper announcement for ABC NO RIO "Animals Living in Cities" featuring Andrea Callard's work., 1980; cuid23124 (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - photograph "Half of the Heart went to Work...", 1980; cuid23125 (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - drawing, "Half of the Heart went to Work. The Other Half went to War.", 1980; cuid23126 (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of trahs, Jeff Callard and Matthew Geller on the West Side highway at Chambers. Negatives in folder 259., 1980; cuid23127 (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - "Whole more than two" Richard Miller and Andrea Callard Show at White Columns., 1981; cuid23128 (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Cummington Community for the Arts, Andrea Callard, Marjorie Cohen, Matthew Geller. Corresponding negatives in folder 268., 1981; cuid23129 (Box 15, Folder 269)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Cummington Community for the Arts. Corresponding contact sheet in folder 270., 1981; cuid23130 (Box 15, Folder 271)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Cummington Community for the Arts. Corresponding negatives in folder 272., 1981; cuid23131 (Box 15, Folder 273)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of hostage parade., 1981; cuid23132 (Box 15, Folder 274)
    - Ailanthus photo collage with trees cut out., 1981; cuid23133 (Box 15, Folder 275)
  - Series II Subseries E: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1982-1986 Lispenard St
    - NYC Wildlife Museum Posters. Curated by Christ Rupp. Includes AC work., 1982; cuid23134 (Box 15, Folder 283)
    - Collection Plate watercolors., 1982; cuid23135 (Box not specified, Folder 284)
    - White Columns Groupshow poster. April 21-May 9, 1982., cuid23136 (Box 15, Folder 285)
    - Black and White contact sheets. Images include More Cardboard Air Band at ABC NO RIO and Colab Mural America at 40 Lispenard., 1982; cuid23137 (Box 15, Folder 286)
    - "Pus Factory" drawings., 1984; cuid23138 (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - Planning drawings and photograph for Kathy High and Andrea Callard's Colab Street poster collaboration., 1984; cuid23139 (Box 15, Folder 302)
    - Black and white contact sheets. Images of Ailanthus trees and an anti-nuclear demonstration., 1984; cuid23140 (Box 15, Folder 304)
    - Women in Jazz Downtown Poster. Designed by Andrea Callard., 1985; cuid23141 (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - Series II Subseries F: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1987-1989 Lispenard St
    - The Summer magazine of Art Awareness. Full page on The Wake Up Printshop with photographs of Andrea Callard and her work., 1987; cuid23142 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Publicity posters for DIA "If you lived here" exhibition, cuid23143 (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Series II Subseries G: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1990-2000 Lispenard St.
    - Art in General window installation, Andrea Callard's "Home Turf" publicity posters, 1990; cuid23144 (Box 16, Folder 359)
    - Storefront for Art and Architecture. Andrea Callard "Designs and ideas for the waste stream" April 26-May 24, 1990, cuid23145 (Box 16, Folder 360)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts. Oversize materials related to folder 378, 1986-1987; cuid23146 (Box 16, Folder 379)
    - Teaching planning diagram., undated; cuid23147 (Box 16, Folder 386)
  - Series II Subseries I: Andrea Callard Artist Files, Miscellaneous materials
    - Art Awareness Summer Season advertisement. Avocet Printshop artist in residence program coordinated by Andrea Callard., undated; cuid23148 (Box 16, Folder 389A)
    - Callard drawing for backyard of ABC NO RIO on Rivington St., undated; cuid23149 (Box 16, Folder 403)
    - Pencil Sketch of trashcan and umbrella, undated; cuid23150 (Box 16, Folder 404)
    - Drawings and writing relating to urban wildlife particularly bugs and birds., undated; cuid23151 (Box 16, Folder 405)
    - drawing and writing, undated; cuid23152 (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - Text, dreawing and watercolor on bristol board, undated; cuid23153 (Box 16, Folder 420)
    - "Holding Hands around a campfire of change", undated; cuid23154 (Box 16, Folder 430)
    - Black and white contact sheets. some annotated., undated; cuid23155 (Box 16, Folder 453)
    - Black and white contact sheets. Images of trashcans., undated; cuid23156 (Box 16, Folder 462)
    - Miscellaneous Black and White photographs. Includes Abbiee Hoffman television images, New York Streets, Statues, bird images, "This is Not Doris Day", Fred Krughoff errand at Phillipson Chambers Xerox Store, Reese Williams and bus., undated; cuid23157 (Box 16, Folder 463A)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of fire hydrants., undated; cuid23158 (Box 16, Folder 481)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of buildings., undated; cuid23159 (Box 16, Folder 484)
  - Subseries III Subseries A: Administrative Materials, Grants
    - Materials relating to Virginia Commonwealth Univeristy artist forum., 1984-1985; cuid23160 (Box 17, Folder 509)
    - Supporting documents to Municipal Arts Society regarding "The Tenement" installation at Chinatown History Project and DIA. Includes photocopies of contact sheets, contact sheets of photo collage, slide show script, slide list and photocopies of exhibited photographs., 1989; cuid23161 (Box 17, Folder 522)
    - Brendan Gill Prize Information, undated; cuid23162 (Box 17, Folder 527)
  - Series III Subseries D: Administrative Materials, Organizational Participation
    - LINE Poster/RFP, Andrea Callard on Board of Directors. [Poster by Andrea Callard?], ca. 1978; cuid23163 (Box 17, Folder 538)
  - Series III Subseries F: Administrative Materials, Notes and Research copies
    - Housing advocacy Met Council on Housing, Tenant/Inquilino newspaper. 19:2, 1989; cuid23164 (Box 17, Folder 547)
  - Series IV Subseries A: Other Artist Files, Individual artist files
    - Ahearn, Charlie. "The Deadly Art of Survival" poster., undated; cuid23165 (Box 17, Folder 563)
    - Ahearn, John. "Shame" film poster., undated; cuid23166 (Box 17, Folder 564)
    - Caldwell, Randi "Line O' Pine" booklet, unbound, unfolded with inscription, undated; cuid23167 (Folder 13)
    - Cooper, Ellen painted care package box. Inside ae papers that may or may not be part of the original care package., 1983; cuid23168 (Box 18, Folder 585)
    - Glier, Mike. "Training for Leisure" at the Kitchen., 1980; cuid23169 (Box 17, Folder 593)
    - Howland, R., undated; cuid23170 (Box 6, Folder 596)
    - Hsieh, Tehching "One Year Performance" poster, 1981-1982; cuid23171 (Box 17, Folder 597)
    - Mock, Richard Basil "Dog on the Eat" artist proof, 1980; cuid23172 (Box 17, Folder 609)
    - Mock, Richard Basil original copies of New York Times artworks., undated; cuid23173 (Box 17, Folder 610)
    - Mock, Richard Basil. Spanner Poster, undated; cuid23174 (Box 17, Folder 611)
    - Nauman, R., undated; cuid23175 (Box 17, Folder 614)
    - Seltman, R. L. Installation and film screening at White Columns., 1980; cuid23176 (Box 17, Folder 624)
    - Thompson, Mark. "Sharing Work in Progress from my Relationship with Honeybees" poster, undated; cuid23177 (Box 17, Folder 630)
    - Wells, David, undated; cuid23178 (Box 17, Folder 637)
  - Series IV Subseries B: Other Artist Files, Collaborations and Group Shows
    - Fitzgibbon and Winters Poster, undated; cuid23179 (Box 17, Folder 643A)
    - Cooney, Robert and Tom Otterneess Collaboration "Gas Grati$" poster, in Spanish., undated; cuid23180 (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Series IV Subseries C: Other Artist Files, Miscellaneous and Unknown Artists
    - "Disarm" poster, undated; cuid23181 (Box 17, Folder 650)
    - "Push and Pull" photo poster, undated; cuid23182 (Box 17, Folder 653)
    - unlabeled poster, television with globe on top, poinsetta flower on top of television., undated; cuid23183 (Box 17, Folder 654)
    - "Half Magic Little Quilts" poster, undated; cuid23184 (Box 17, Folder 655)
    - Poster, white text on black background, drawing of castle architecture., undated; cuid23185 (Box 17, Folder 656)
    - Child's drawing, undated; cuid23186 (Box 17, Folder 658)
    - Black and white contact sheet, corresponds to negatives in folder 569, undated; cuid23187 (Box 17, Folder 660)
    - Unlabeled poster, spraypaint, stencil, diagrams of muscle and skeletal systems., undated; cuid23188 (Box 17, Folder 662)
  - Series VI: Biographical Material
    - Journal entry- personal writing, undated; cuid23189 (Box 17, Folder 844)
  - Series VII: Printed Materials